

Contact information

Email

juananmgz@gmail.com

Address

- Salamanca
- Madrid

Telephone

(+34) 658 016121

Nacionality

Spanish (Española)

Links

- juananmgz.github.io
- linkedin.com/in/juananmgz

Competences

Social skills

Quick learning

Commitment Agile

development

Strategy

Initiative

Leadership

Organization

Performance

Responsibility

Teamwork

Languages

Spanish: Native

English: Intermediate Level

More info

Driving License own **Car**

Juan Antonio Muñoz Gómez

Frontend (Full Stack) Developer

Specialized in (mostly Frontend) Web Development and Agile Methodologies. My preferences are User Interface and User Experience Design (UI & UX) based on Human-Computer Interaction. My goal is to make intuitive and user-friendly as well as creative and immersive websites.

Experience

Madrid, Spain

Apr 2022 - Currently

Salamanca, Spain Feb 2021 - Jul 2021 Frontend Developer

Monobo

Web Applications and Electronics Developer
ESALab Research Group ⋅ Curricular Internships

Education

Alcalá de Henares, Spain Sept 2021 - Sept 2022 Master in Agile Software Web Development
University of Alcalá de Henares

Average Grade: 9,02/10

Salamanca, Spain Sept 2017 - Jul 2021 Degree in Computer Engineering
 University of Salamanca

10.0 Honour Mention - Final Degree Project

Formative Courses & Certificates

- Mongo + Express. API Optimization. Udemy (2022)
- BEM CSS + ITCSS = BEMIT Methodology Advanced Web Design. Udemy (2022)
- Scrum Master: Agile project management with Scrum. Viewnext (2021)
- Business and Marketing Plan. Industrial and Intellectual Property. Operations and Human Resources Plan. Fund. General USAL - Plan TCUE (2021)
- Ionic React: Cross-Platform Mobile Development with Ionic 5. Udemy ESALab (2021)

Other Formative Experiences

- English Native Language Immersion. Edinburgh (2014)
- Musical education [18+ years]. Various associations & instructors (2003-Currently)

Competencies

WEB DEVELOPMENT

- Basic Languages: HTML, CSS, JS, TS, JSON, YAML, PHP, Java, XML
- Frontend: NodeJS, Bootstrap, SASS, JQuery, Angular, VueJS, React, EJS

→ Inmersive Frontend: (3D) Spline, WebGL / (Animations) Parallax Effects, SVG

- DevOps & CI/CD: Docker, Kubernetes, Istio, JUnit, Maven, Selenium, SonarQube, Heroku
- BackEnd: Express, Spring + Eureka, Servlets, JPA, APIs REST, Perl / Apache, NGinx
 L, DDBB: Mongo + ODM (Mongoose), MySQL / MariaDB + ORM (TypeORM), FireBase
- UX & Prototyping: Adobe XD, Figma, InVision, SketchUp

WORKING METHODOLOGIES

- Scrum + Kanban + Lean + XP: Scrum Master. Jira, Taiga, Mic. Project
- **BEMIT:** BEM + ITCSS
- Version Control: Git → GitHub, GitLab (+ DevOps Method.)

Awards & Recognisements

- ICE 2021 Business Project Cultural Entrepreneurship Discipline, FUESCyL (2022)
- TCUE Market Oriented Prototypes Grant, Fund. General USAL (2021)
- Traditional Music Award Young Talent, Arlafolk (2019)

Articles

Available at orcid.com: 0000-0001-6794-5445